[

FreeFileSync Open Source File Synchronization
=============================================](https://freefilesync.org/)

[  
Download](https://freefilesync.org/download.php) [Archive](https://freefilesync.org/archive.php)

 [ Forum

Report Bugs  
Discuss Features](https://freefilesync.org/forum/)

**It looks like an ad blocker has blocked the ads.** [](https://freefilesync.org/donate#support) The FreeFileSync project is 100% dependent on ad revenue and donations to stay alive. Instead of the ads, and after FreeFileSync has proven useful to you, please think about supporting with a donation. 

Privacy Policy
--------------

We respect the privacy of our visitors. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information that are collected and recorded by freefilesync.org and how they are used. Please direct all questions regarding this policy to[\[Turn on JavaScript to see the email address\]](#).  

### Log Files

Like many other websites, freefilesync.org makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors of the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information is not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  

### FreeFileSync Forum

This section explains in detail how the "FreeFileSync Forum" (hereinafter "we", "us", "FreeFileSync Forum", "https://freefilesync.org/forum") and phpBB (hereinafter "phpBB software") use any information collected during any session of usage by you (hereinafter "your information").  
  
Your information is collected via two ways. Firstly, browsing the "FreeFileSync Forum" will cause the phpBB software to create a number of cookies, which are small text files that are downloaded on to your computer’s web browser temporary files. The first two cookies just contain a user identifier (hereinafter "user-id") and an anonymous session identifier (hereinafter "session-id"), automatically assigned to you by the phpBB software. A third cookie will be created once you have browsed topics within the "FreeFileSync Forum" and is used to store which topics have been read, thereby improving your user experience.  
  
We may also create cookies external to the phpBB software whilst browsing the "FreeFileSync Forum", though these are outside the scope of this section which is intended to only cover the pages created by the phpBB software. The second way in which we collect your information is by what you submit to us. This can be, and is not limited to: posting as an anonymous user, registering on the "FreeFileSync Forum" (hereinafter "your account") and posts submitted by you after registration and whilst logged in (hereinafter "your posts").  
  
Your account will at a bare minimum contain a uniquely identifiable name (hereinafter "your user name"), a personal password used for logging into your account (hereinafter "your password") and a personal, valid email address (hereinafter "your email"). Your information for your account at the "FreeFileSync Forum" is protected by data-protection laws applicable in the country that hosts us. Any information beyond your user name, your password, and your email address required by the "FreeFileSync Forum" during the registration process is either mandatory or optional, at the discretion of the "FreeFileSync Forum". In all cases, you have the option of what information in your account is publicly displayed. Furthermore, within your account, you have the option to opt-in or opt-out of automatically generated emails from the phpBB software.  
  
Your password is ciphered (a one-way hash) so that it is secure. However, it is recommended that you do not reuse the same password across a number of different websites. Your password is the means of accessing your account at the "FreeFileSync Forum", so please guard it carefully and under no circumstance will anyone affiliated with the "FreeFileSync Forum", phpBB or another 3rd party, legitimately ask you for your password. Should you forget your password for your account, you can use the "I forgot my password" feature provided by the phpBB software. This process will ask you to submit your user name and your email, then the phpBB software will generate a new password to reclaim your account.  

### Our Advertising Partners

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads on freefilesync.org. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our site's visitors based on their visit to freefilesync.org and/or other sites on the internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Google Ad Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/).  
Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on freefilesync.org and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.  
  
freefilesync.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.  

### Third Party Privacy Policies

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. freefilesync.org's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites:  

* [YouTube Privacy Guidelines](https://www.youtube.com/t/privacy) (embedded demo videos)
* [Google Privacy Policies](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) (AdSense website advertisements)

### Financial Contributions

In order to comply with accounting regulations, the following personal data related to donations is stored: transaction id, email, donor name, and donation amount.  
Regarding payments for the FreeFileSync Business Edition the following information is stored: transaction id, email, buyer name, company name, address, VAT ID (only for EU), and payment amount.  
In order to enable software features of the FreeFileSync "Donation Edition" and FreeFileSync "Business Edition" (calculation of update interval, device count determination, email notifications), user name and hardware id are recorded during the first start of the respective FreeFileSync edition. This personal data will be used exclusively for the purposes described here, and not made accessible to third parties. In the case of email notifications, the email content is not stored by the freefilesync.org server and is directly forwarded for delivery.  

### Children's Information

freefilesync.org does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that freefilesync.org has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.  

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.  

### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.  

### Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Sep 12, 2023  

Copyright © 2024 Zenju:[\[Turn on JavaScript to see the email address\]](#)
